http://www.plasmapure.com/t-privacy.aspx

Login
View Cart (0)
View Wishlist (0)
COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY ON THE INTERNET
Mitsubishi Electric Trane HVAC US (“METUS”) respects privacy issues on the Internet. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) summarizes how METUS treats information it collects when you access this website (“Site”). As a visitor to our Site, the Policy serves to inform you of the types of information we collect, how we collect such information, whether we disclose it to any third parties, your ability to control how such information is used, and your right to correct any inaccurate information we collect about you.
SCOPE OF APPLICATION
The Policy applies to METUS’s Site located at http://www.mitsubishicomfort.com/, as well as all other websites, domains, services, applications, and products owned and operated by METUS. In cases where certain METUS programs, products and services operate under a different privacy statement, such a policy may supersede or supplement this one. The Policy does not apply to the websites of other companies or organizations to which the METUS Site links.
LINKS TO NON-MITSUBISHI WEBSITES
This Site may provide links that offer convenient access to third-party products, services, applications or other websites not affiliated with METUS. Clicking these links will cause you to leave the METUS Site and be transferred to websites owned and operated by unaffiliated third parties. METUS will make an earnest effort to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, but we have no control over any third party websites or their privacy policies (which may differ from that of METUS). We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites or products, and the Policy does not apply to any information you may choose to share with third party websites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any such third parties before disclosing personal information on their website.
The Site may at times allow you to share information with a social media network through certain social media features. By using these features, specific information may be collected and shared based on the utility of a given feature.  METUS encourages you to review the privacy policies and settings of any such social media sites with which you interact so that you understand how any information collected through the social media network might be utilized.
NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION
In general, you can visit this Site without revealing any personal information about yourself. However, we do collect information on user habits that helps improve the products, services, content, and advertising offered on our Site. We do so in ways that do not personally identify any single visitor. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. If we do combine non-personal information with personal information, the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains conjoined.
COOKIES AND HOW THEY ARE USED
METUS collects visitor data to analyze and understand important trends and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may choose to use this information in our marketing and advertising services.  To achieve this end, METUS may utilize a technology referred to as “cookies” to ascertain various user habits such as the number of people who visit our Site, average browsing time, the number of time our Site is accessed, and how much of the Site is viewed.  A cookie is a tiny data file transferred by a website to your computer’s hard drive for the purpose of storing small amounts of information. METUS collects information in aggregate for statistical purposes to improve our Site and better personalize your user experience. METUS does not review information on individuals themselves.
A cookie can be described as either “session” or “tracking.” Session cookies are deleted after closing your browser.  Tracking cookies remain on your computer until you delete them or upon expiration.  METUS does not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information and does not combine information collected through cookies with other personally identifiable information in an attempt to expose your identity, screen name, e-mail address or any other personal information.
You can set your browser to send notifications before you receive a cookie, which gives you the ability to decide whether or not to accept it. You can also choose to accept or refuse cookies by changing the settings on your browser. Because browsers vary, you should check your browser’s “Help” menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences.  If you do so, however, areas of some sites may not function properly.
COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION AND HOW WE USE IT
Federal and state laws require us to disclose how we collect, use, share, and protect your personal information. The law also limits how we can use your personal information. Personally identifiable information that METUS may collect includes (1) first and last name; (2) physical address; (3) e-mail address; (4) telephone number; (5) social security number; (6) any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of a specific individual; and (7) information concerning a user that a website or online service collects online from the user and maintains in personally identifiable form in combination with an identifier described above. The term may also extend to details such as a person’s birthday, height, weight or hair color that are collected online and stored by an operator in personally identifiable form.
In cases where information related to social security numbers is collected, METUS will take all necessary precautions to protect the user’s privacy by (1) protecting the confidentiality of any and all social security numbers, (2) prohibiting unlawful disclosure of social security numbers, and (3) limiting access to social security numbers.
There may be times when METUS needs to collect, export, and use personal information, as defined above, in the course of conducting normal business activities. Personal information will be collected, exported and used for reasons including, but not limited to, the following: (a) managing our relationship with you; (b) collecting information when you register to use customer and/or vendor specific services; (c) communicating with you about METUS products or services; (d) ordering a product or requesting assistance in completing a transaction; (e) completing a contact/inquiry form; and (f) inquiring about a product or speaking with a customer service agent. This information helps us better manage our relationship with you and allows METUS to personalize your experience and interaction on our Site. In such cases, you may be required to provide your name, Internet address, screen name, billing address, credit card number or other personally identifiable information so that METUS can complete a business transaction or fulfill an obligation to you. METUS will always specify on its Site how we intend to use any information we receive and will proceed with appropriate notice and consent, when necessary.  If you do not wish to receive information on various other products or services that might be of interest to you, METUS offers the ability to opt out via the registration screen or by directly contacting the Webmaster.
When you initiate contact with METUS regarding an issue or problem, any personal information you provide is voluntary. We collect and use only the minimum information necessary to effectively respond to your concern and/or to conduct an investigation. When METUS directly solicits personal information from you in writing, we will specify how the information will be used and will proceed with appropriate notice and consent, if necessary. If you choose to post or share personal information, including photographs, on any public form on the Site, please be aware that any information you submit can be read, viewed, collected, or used by other forums user. METUS retains no control over any individuals who may subsequently contact or send unsolicited messages to you and is not responsible for the personal information you choose to provide in these forums.
When you provide us with personal information, we may keep a record of the inquiry. In addition, we may store and process personal information and share it with our worldwide subsidiaries and affiliates to better understand your needs and improve our relationship with you.  METUS does not use or disclose information gathered from individual visits to the Site or information you provide to METUS to any third parties with the intention to sell, rent or otherwise market your personal information. METUS may, however, share your personal information with other companies, organizations or individuals if, under a good faith belief, we believe that the access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to (a) meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request; (b) enforce applicable terms of service, including investigation of potential violations; (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; and (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of METUS, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.
METUS may at times employ a third party service provider to perform or assist with on-line surveys, contests, sweepstakes or other promotions, which may include help with administering the survey or promotion, compiling the data or providing customer support. These parties will be required to sign a non-disclosure agreement prior to performing any services with METUS and will be legally obligated not to disclose any personal information received from you.  When we conduct a survey, we will make every effort to let you know how the information will be collected and used.
You have the option not to provide personal information to METUS. If you choose not to provide the personal information we request, you can still visit most of the Site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers and services that involve our interaction with you.
CHILDREN
The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"), as well as various other state laws, prohibits unfair or deceptive acts or practices in connection with the collection, use, and/or disclosure of personal information from and about children on the Internet. METUS does not knowingly collect information from children nor does it target its Site or mobile applications to children less than 13 years of age. Children without the consent of their parent or guardian should not submit personal Information to the Site. If we discover that we have collected the personal information of a child, as defined by law, we will take immediate steps to handle that information in accordance with the law. Any minor under 18 years of age may also remove, or request and obtain removal of, online content that is collected and stored when such information is submitted by the user by directly contacting the Webmaster. METUS encourages all parents or guardians to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of their personal information while using the Internet.
CHOICES IN SELECTING PRIVACY PREFERENCES
You may, at your discretion, subscribe to and receive information related to METUS products and services, including general METUS communications by postal mail, email, telephone, or mobile device. You also have the right to make or change these preferences at any time. This option does not apply to communications primarily for the purpose of administering order completion, contracts, support, product safety warnings, or other administrative and transactional notices where the primary purpose of these communications is not promotional in nature.
ACCESS TO AND ACCURACY OF YOUR INFORMATION
METUS wants to ensure that it accurately records your personal information. You have the right to request the disclosure of your personal information in our possession and mandate revisions when necessary. METUS offers you ways to quickly update and/or to delete incorrect information, barring the need to retain it for legitimate business or legal purposes. In order to update your personal information, METUS may, for your personal protection, require you to verify your identity before we honor the request.  In cases where the request is unreasonably repetitive, requires disproportionate technical effort, risks the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical, METUS may reject the request and work with you to find an alternative solution.  Please note that requests made over the phone may be recorded to ensure proper response to your request.
To view and change the personal information that you directly provided to METUS, return to the web page where you originally submitted your data and follow the instructions on that web page or contact METUS directly for assistance. METUS will respond to any such request in an appropriate manner and within a reasonable timeframe.
METUS operates in such a way to protect information from accidental or malicious destruction.  As such, subsequent to your request to delete personal information from our system, we reserve the right to retain residual copies from our active servers for a short period of time and may not remove information from our backup systems.
METUS ADS AND OFFERINGS ON THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES
METUS may contract with service providers to place ads on websites owned by third parties. In addition, some websites may be “powered by” a service provider to provide METUS offers on METUS’s behalf.  These service providers may send cookies and use web beacons on these third-party websites and on our Site. The cookies and web beacons may enable METUS to collect information about the pages you viewed and the links you clicked.
Most web browsers offer you the ability to inform websites and ad networks that you do not want your online activities tracked through a “Do Not Track” feature. Your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a "Do Not Track" signal to online services you visit. Note, however, there is no consensus among industry participants as to what "Do Not Track" means in this context. Like many online services, METUS does not currently alter its practices when it receives a "Do Not Track" signal from a visitor’s browser.
To find out more about "Do Not Track," you can visit http://www.aboutads.info/ to learn more about network advertising and your choices for opting out. However, METUS is not responsible for the completeness or accuracy of this third party information.  Some third parties, however, may offer you choices regarding their tracking technologies. METUS is not responsible for the completeness or accuracy of third party choice notices or choice mechanisms.
NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES
Our Policy may change from time to time.  If METUS decides to change its Policy, those changes will be posted in this section to keep you updated on the types of information we collect, how we collect such information, whether we disclose it to any third parties, your ability to control how such information is used, and your right to correct any erroneous information collected about you.  When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Policy.
QUESTIONS OR COMMENTS
We value your opinion and feedback about of services and policy. If you have any questions or concerns about our Policy and how it might affect you personally, please contact the Webmaster at 'Contact Us' button located on our homepage.
OUR COMPANYWIDE COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY
Because we value our commitment to information security, we communicate our privacy and security guidelines to METUS employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.
YOUR CONSENT
By using this Site, you consent to the terms of our privacy statement and to our collecting and processing of personal information for the purposes given above.
Customer Service
Contact Us
Order Tracking
Wishlist
Your Account
Store Policies & Info
Shipping
Returns
Payment Methods
© 2014-2020. Mitsubishi Electric Cooling & Heating. All Rights Reserved.
View wishlist
Shopping Cart:
0
Items
Your shopping cart is currently empty.Note to AspDotNetStorefront Administrators:You can edit this placeholder text by editing the "EmptyCartText" topic within the Admin Console.
Discounts:
Total:
$0.00
Close
Checkout
View cart
Your Wishlist:
0
Items
Your wish list is currently empty. Note to AspDotNetStorefront Administrators:You can edit this placeholder text by editing the "EmptyWishListText" topic within the Admin Console.
Total:
$0.00
Close
Move all to Cart
Loading...
